<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Cosmiqo</title>
    <link>https://cosmiqo.com/</link>
    <description>Recent content on Cosmiqo</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Tue, 26 Sep 2017 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="https://cosmiqo.com/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Roadway lighting measurement with Litesense</title>
      <link>https://cosmiqo.com/article/on-litesense-runs/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 26 Sep 2017 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://cosmiqo.com/article/on-litesense-runs/</guid>
      <description>To ensure that ensure that roadway lighting is uniform, roadway lighting measurement needs to be done for every road and every lane. A picture is worth a thousand words but videos are worth much more.
 How roadway lighting measurement with Litesense is done   The yellow moving arrow depicts the Litesense vehicle when taking measurements of the surrounding street lights and the yellow trace is the path that was traversed for the night.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Attraction occupancy at Sentosa (Part 3 of 3)</title>
      <link>https://cosmiqo.com/article/on-sentosa-03/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 16 Jul 2017 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://cosmiqo.com/article/on-sentosa-03/</guid>
      <description>In Part 2, we discussed queues and how such information can be used by both visitors and operations. An additional parameter that would be useful for planning would be that of occupancy.
Why is occupancy important? Occupancy is the number of people in a particular area. The more people there are, the more crowded it becomes. This may result in a safety concern and certain level of discomfort (for some).</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Attraction queueing times at Sentosa (Part 2 of 3)</title>
      <link>https://cosmiqo.com/article/on-sentosa-02/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 15 Jul 2017 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://cosmiqo.com/article/on-sentosa-02/</guid>
      <description>In Part 1, we concluded by providing some insights into when and where crowds will form across several entrances and attractions as a result of visitorship prediction. We now shift the discussion to attractions.
Why do queues form? Queues are fascinating and it has become a part of our lives. It forms because of three reasons:
  customers arrive faster than they can be serviced
  the number of service staff are insufficient and/or inefficient</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Predicting visitorship at Sentosa (Part 1 of 3)</title>
      <link>https://cosmiqo.com/article/on-sentosa-01/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 27 Jun 2017 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://cosmiqo.com/article/on-sentosa-01/</guid>
      <description>Sentosa is an island resort off the southern coast of Singapore, connected to the city by road, cable car, pedestrian boardwalk and monorail. As an iconic leisure destination, Sentosa had the pleasure of welcoming 19.5 million guests last year. With that many guests, having a strong operations team would come in handy.
As a general rule of thumb, the effort required to streamline operations is only 1/4 that of external activities.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Going to Cheras for supper</title>
      <link>https://cosmiqo.com/article/on-roadeye-cheras/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 25 Jun 2017 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://cosmiqo.com/article/on-roadeye-cheras/</guid>
      <description>Over the past couple of months, we were developing RoadEyeTM, a low-cost road roughness monitoring device. The idea behind RoadEyeTM is simple - allow quick and easy road roughess monitoring across a large network without disrupting traffic flow. Some of our early trials were performed from a drive that we took from Subang Jaya to Cheras in Malaysia.
Indicators for roughness level are
 Smoothest Smoother Smooth Normal Rough Rougher Roughest  Please feel free to interact with the map.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Street Lighting along Persiaran Multimedia, Cyberjaya</title>
      <link>https://cosmiqo.com/article/on-cyberjaya/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 25 Jun 2017 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://cosmiqo.com/article/on-cyberjaya/</guid>
      <description>At the end of 2016, we were told that accidents frequently occur at night along Persiaran Multimedia, Cyberjaya. This could be due to many factors one of which is lighting conditions, a factor that is designed and controllable (you can see where this article is going). We took Litesense® out for a spin.
Accidents are undesirable and with that in mind, we performed roadway lighting measurement for each lane along Persiaran Multimedia.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Ensuring ride quality</title>
      <link>https://cosmiqo.com/article/on-road-roughness/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 24 Jun 2017 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://cosmiqo.com/article/on-road-roughness/</guid>
      <description>Roads have always been a part of our lives. As usual, we never really think much about it until we hit a pothole or come across an unbearably rough stretch of road.
In the early 1980s the highway engineering community identified road roughness as the primary indicator of the utility for a highway network to road users. This is because the roughness of the road surface affects the ride quality and vehicle operating costs.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Our journey to Litesense (Part 3 of 3)</title>
      <link>https://cosmiqo.com/article/on-litesense-03/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 22 Dec 2016 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://cosmiqo.com/article/on-litesense-03/</guid>
      <description>The Automated Street Light Measurement System (ASLMS) (see [Part 2](../on-litesense-02/)) is, in its crudest form, an in-vehicle data acquisition system that outputs geospatial lighting statistics. In its more complex form, the ASLMS comprises:
   a data fusion engine that integrates data from multi-modality sensors into a consistent, accurate, and useful representation, and
  a data analytics engine that examines data with the purpose of drawing conclusions about that information</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Our journey to Litesense (Part 2 of 3)</title>
      <link>https://cosmiqo.com/article/on-litesense-02/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 21 Dec 2016 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://cosmiqo.com/article/on-litesense-02/</guid>
      <description>In Part 1, we ended with the need to carry out illuminance measurements in the wee hours of the morning to reduce the risk of accidents. What we neglected to mention was that even during these hours, carrying out measurement activities requires vigilance since standing in the middle of a road is a pre-requisite. There is also the little known fact that there exists an intersection between people who drive and people who stress-relieve in GTA (see Figure 1).</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Our journey to Litesense (Part 1 of 3)</title>
      <link>https://cosmiqo.com/article/on-litesense-01/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 20 Dec 2016 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://cosmiqo.com/article/on-litesense-01/</guid>
      <description>For those of us who grew up in cities, street lights have always been a part of our lives. Truth be told, we never really think much about it until we stumble across an area that is either too dark or too bright. Yes, most people take street lighting for granted even though humans (like some bugs) are naturally attracted to light.
In the early civilisations, light primarily serves the purpose of security, both to protect the wanderer from tripping or keeping potential robbers at bay.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Street Lighting from Kota Damansara to Centrepoint Bandar Utama</title>
      <link>https://cosmiqo.com/article/on-kd-to-bu/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 05 Mar 2016 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://cosmiqo.com/article/on-kd-to-bu/</guid>
      <description>After producing a light map of the roads around Kota Damansara with the awesome folks from the Sinar Project, we decided to continue using Litesense® for the journey back to Centrepoint Bandar Utama, our earlier rendezvous location.
We asked Waze for the best way back and it responded with a perfect route.
In the map below, the
 green marker is the start point red marker is the end point different colours represent varying brightness levels (measured in lux)  Indicators for brightness level are</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Street Lighting at Ulu Pandan and Bukit Timah</title>
      <link>https://cosmiqo.com/article/on-ulu-pandan/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 20 Feb 2016 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://cosmiqo.com/article/on-ulu-pandan/</guid>
      <description>15th of February in the year 590 was an important one as Khosrow II was crowned king of Persia. About 1400 years later, the night of 15th of February in the year 2016 was also an important one as Litesense® was taken out to ensure that the streets of Ulu Pandan and Bukit Timah were safe for us to drive on, ride, cycle and walk along.
Results of the mission were visualised in Folium, a project &amp;ldquo;that makes it easy to visualize data that&amp;rsquo;s been manipulated in Python on an interactive Leaflet map&amp;rdquo;.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Street Lighting at Kota Damansara</title>
      <link>https://cosmiqo.com/article/on-kota-damansara/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 14 Feb 2016 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://cosmiqo.com/article/on-kota-damansara/</guid>
      <description>Just before the Lunar New Year weekend, we decided to take Litesense® out for a spin with some awesome folks from the Sinar Project. The mission was to produce a light map of the roads around Kota Damansara, a township located in Petaling Jaya, Selangor, Malaysia.
To visualise the results of the mission, we leveraged on Folium, a project &amp;ldquo;that makes it easy to visualize data that&amp;rsquo;s been manipulated in Python on an interactive Leaflet map&amp;rdquo;.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The Importance of Park Lighting</title>
      <link>https://cosmiqo.com/article/on-park-lighting/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 29 Jan 2016 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://cosmiqo.com/article/on-park-lighting/</guid>
      <description>The National Parks Board recently marked the 25th anniversary of the Park Connector Network (PCN) in Singapore. With over 300 km (with the aim to grow the PCN to 360 km by 2020) and an island-wide network that cuts across major parks, nature sites and housing estates, it is imperative that lighting conditions are optimal. To promote safer parks, the single most requested physical design modification to improve safety is usually an increase in lighting.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The Purpose of Street Lighting</title>
      <link>https://cosmiqo.com/article/on-street-lighting/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 25 Jan 2016 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://cosmiqo.com/article/on-street-lighting/</guid>
      <description>At Cosmiqo, we develop technology that audits how bright the roads are by measuring the intensity of street lights. We do this by collecting quite a lot of data, wirelessly streaming it back to our cloud platform and processing this information through our analytics engine. We call this technology Litesense®.
The principal purpose of street lighting is to produce quick, accurate and comfortable visibility at night. These qualities of visibility may safeguard, facilitate and encourage vehicular and pedestrian traffic.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>About Cosmiqo</title>
      <link>https://cosmiqo.com/about.html</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://cosmiqo.com/about.html</guid>
      <description>Founded in 2013 in the trade hub of Singapore, Cosmiqo seeks to empower global supply chains with analytics and optimization engines enabling increased productivity, orchestration and visibility for supply chain operations.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Contact Us</title>
      <link>https://cosmiqo.com/contact.html</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://cosmiqo.com/contact.html</guid>
      <description>Get in touch with us. We&amp;rsquo;d love to hear from you.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Contact Us</title>
      <link>https://cosmiqo.com/thankyou.html</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://cosmiqo.com/thankyou.html</guid>
      <description>Get in touch with usWe&#39;d love to hear from youThank you for contacting us. We will get in touch with you soon.Singapore10 Anson Road, International Plaza
#33-04A
Singapore 079903Shah Alam, SelangorNo. 13-M (Mezzanine Floor)
Jalan Tengku Ampuan Zabedah J9/J
Shah Alam
Selangor, 40100 Malaysia</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Cosmiqo Addresses Today&#39;s Warehousing Challenges</title>
      <link>https://cosmiqo.com/solutions.html</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://cosmiqo.com/solutions.html</guid>
      <description>Learn how Cosmiqo addresses today&amp;rsquo;s warehousing challenges.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Cosmiqo Litesense®</title>
      <link>https://cosmiqo.com/litesense.html</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://cosmiqo.com/litesense.html</guid>
      <description>Real-time data collection. Lamp identification and intensity mapping on-the-go.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Credits</title>
      <link>https://cosmiqo.com/credits.html</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://cosmiqo.com/credits.html</guid>
      <description>Credits. Where it is due.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Elevate current operations with</title>
      <link>https://cosmiqo.com/iris_people.html</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://cosmiqo.com/iris_people.html</guid>
      <description>Improve material and process flow orchestration, optimization and visibility for your human-centric warehouses.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Join the team. Make a difference.</title>
      <link>https://cosmiqo.com/careers.html</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://cosmiqo.com/careers.html</guid>
      <description>Join the team. Make a difference.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Leadership</title>
      <link>https://cosmiqo.com/leadership.html</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://cosmiqo.com/leadership.html</guid>
      <description>Our trail-blazing team have been involved in running global supply chains, enabling the technological evolution of logistics and are at the forefront of some of its largest strategic changes.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>MAVIS™</title>
      <link>https://cosmiqo.com/mavis.html</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://cosmiqo.com/mavis.html</guid>
      <description>Machine Visibility. MAVIS™ provides full visibility of operations through a resilient sensing backbone and powerful analytics engine.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Newsroom</title>
      <link>https://cosmiqo.com/newsroom.html</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://cosmiqo.com/newsroom.html</guid>
      <description>We are trusted by the world&amp;rsquo;s leading companies and industry-leading partners. Find out what Cosmiqo has been up to and reach out to the press team.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Plan assets and execute operations with certainty</title>
      <link>https://cosmiqo.com/iris_simulator.html</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://cosmiqo.com/iris_simulator.html</guid>
      <description>IRIS Warehouse Simulator enables data-driven warehousing assets and operation planning for the most accurate allocation of resources possible.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Take Advantage of Our Partner Ecosystem</title>
      <link>https://cosmiqo.com/partners.html</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://cosmiqo.com/partners.html</guid>
      <description>Cosmiqo partners are the foundation of our success. We connect you with top partners to help you meet your technology goals, access implementation and integration with Cosmiqo-as-a-service.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Tomorrow’s Fulfilment, Today.</title>
      <link>https://cosmiqo.com/products.html</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://cosmiqo.com/products.html</guid>
      <description>IRIS is tomorrow&amp;rsquo;s fulfilment, today. IRIS™ is the backbone for Cosmiqo’s A.I. and proprietary algorithms used in decision-making.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Transform robotic operations with</title>
      <link>https://cosmiqo.com/iris_rc.html</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://cosmiqo.com/iris_rc.html</guid>
      <description>Re-imagine material and process flow orchestration, optimization and visibility for your robot-centric warehouses and manufacturing shop floors.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Why Cosmiqo?</title>
      <link>https://cosmiqo.com/why_cosmiqo.html</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://cosmiqo.com/why_cosmiqo.html</guid>
      <description>Cosmiqo helps organizations remove material and process flow inefficiencies through orchestration, optimization and visibility for human loose-picking &amp;amp; robot warehousing.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>