<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Tops on Cosmiqo</title>
    <link>http://cosmiqo.com/top/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Tops on Cosmiqo</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    
	<atom:link href="http://cosmiqo.com/top/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>About</title>
      <link>http://cosmiqo.com/about.html</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://cosmiqo.com/about.html</guid>
      <description>About us.  A team of technology enthuasists that specialises in supply chain analytics and operations management innovation.      Management Team   Koh Niak Wu, Ph.D. LinkedIn  Founder, CEO + CTO  Dr Koh specialises in supply chain analytics, strategy execution and operations management innovation. He is an Intellectual Transcendences recipient recognised by the Asian Productivity Organisation and the China Productivity Centre.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Ampsense</title>
      <link>http://cosmiqo.com/amp.html</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://cosmiqo.com/amp.html</guid>
      <description>Energy analytics.
For a sustainable future.  Do it for our children.
     Cosmiqo Ampsense®.
Effective energy monitoring. Real-time data collection. Monitor, process and visualise energy and temperature data. Anywhere.        Purpose  Cosmiqo Ampsense® was designed to provide analytical insights on power consumption. It provides current usage and details out system energy efficiency.
  Benefits  More than we realise.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Articles</title>
      <link>http://cosmiqo.com/articles.html</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://cosmiqo.com/articles.html</guid>
      <description>Articles.  Sharing and Learning.      On Lighting  Roadway lighting measurement with Litesense
Street Lighting along Persiaran Multimedia, Cyberjaya
Our journey to Litesense (Part 3 of 3)
Our journey to Litesense (Part 2 of 3)
Our journey to Litesense (Part 1 of 3)
Street Lighting from Kota Damansara to Centrepoint Bandar Utama
Street lighting at Ulu Pandan and Bukit Timah
Street lighting at Kota Damansara</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Careers</title>
      <link>http://cosmiqo.com/careers.html</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://cosmiqo.com/careers.html</guid>
      <description>Join the team.
Make a difference.  Cosmiqo is a humble start-up that creates innovative technology simply to make people smile more. We are always nice to sentient beings and place ethics at the core of our values. Engineers at heart, the team is always looking out for unique ways to enhance the quality of life.      We&#39;re hiring   There are some pretty fun and pioneering projects up in the pipeline.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Credits</title>
      <link>http://cosmiqo.com/credits.html</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://cosmiqo.com/credits.html</guid>
      <description>Credits.  Where it is due.      Photos  Highway photo from Splitshire
Street lamp photo from Splitshire
Toy car photo from DesignersPics
Remaining photos from Unsplash
  Icons  Micons from Cosmin Negoita on Iconjar
Flat icons from Icons8
Social Media icons from Stephen Morley
Web and E-commerce icons from Pavel Kozlov on Gumroad
User icon created by Cris Dobbins from the Noun Project</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>IRIS Router</title>
      <link>http://cosmiqo.com/router.html</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://cosmiqo.com/router.html</guid>
      <description>Warehouse Pick Path Optimisation.  Be Efficient.
     IRIS Router™ Order picking has been identified as a major activity within a warehouse and it consumes about 55% of total warehouse operating costs. Additionally, pickers spend about 55% to 70% of time travelling during order picking. IRIS Router increases picking efficiency by providing superior pick-paths that reduces the travelling distance.    Main Features  COST EFFECTIVE  Performance-based</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Litesense</title>
      <link>http://cosmiqo.com/litesense.html</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://cosmiqo.com/litesense.html</guid>
      <description>City-wide analytics.
For street lighting.  The measurement of street lighting intensity has always been manual. That’s right. Handheld lux meter, standing in the middle of the road, trying not to get hit, trying to get decent readings. Trying again. And again.
We’ve changed the way it works.
     Cosmiqo Litesense®.
Be productive. Be safe. Real-time data collection. Lamp identification and intensity mapping on-the-go.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>MAVIS</title>
      <link>http://cosmiqo.com/mavis.html</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://cosmiqo.com/mavis.html</guid>
      <description>Manufacturing Visibility  Be Visible.
     MAVIS™ MAVIS™ is an integrated software/hardware platform that enables the Industry 4.0 journey. MAVIS™ provides full visibility of operations through a resilient sensing backbone and powerful analytics engine. Other application areas that will benefit from such visibility include warehouses, manufacturing sites, smart cities and logistics systems.     Main Features  COST EFFECTIVE  Value-adding, compact and modular system</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>